I just…
wanted to escape
the bullying
Why did things
turn out like this?
Hey, Hong Il-tak
Kim Hyeong-ju
wants to see you
Okay
Hey, Hyeon-wu, Hong Il-tak
was called to the roof
by Hyeong-ju
They're going
to beat him up
because he's gotten
too cocky
Are you Lee Hyeon-wu?
I can't study when
things
aren't organized
So I'm here
to clean things up
Bring it on
when you're ready
Where is he?
Where's Kim Hyeong-ju?
He's not here
What?
I called you here
He's going to beat up
Lee Hyeon-wu
and you were
the only way to lure him
I'm heading back
Where do you think
you're going?
Didn't you want
to stop being
Lee Hyeon-wu's lackey?
I hadn't thought
that far ahead
But I don't feel good
about Hyeon-wu
getting beaten up
Let me go
Please
Are you really
dating Lee Hyeon-wu?
You
disgusting b******